[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "Are they of the belief that this is in the end, going to be a force for good or do they believe as many Republicans would have us believe that this is really deeply troublesome?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "of", "the", "belief", "that", "this", "is", "in", "the", "end", ",", "going", "to", "be", "a", "force", "for", "good", "or", "do", "they", "believe", "as", "many", "Republicans", "would", "have", "us", "believe", "that", "this", "is", "really", "deeply", "troublesome", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "You know, it's interesting and it's very hard as you might imagine, Piers to think any large community including the medical one with one broad brush.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "and", "it", "'s", "very", "hard", "as", "you", "might", "imagine", ",", "Piers", "to", "think", "any", "large", "community", "including", "the", "medical", "one", "with", "one", "broad", "brush", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", ":"], "qSentId": 21, "question": "UPTA: The President did say that he was angry about this, I mean, do you know when he first knew that there was a problem?", "question_tokens": ["UPTA", ":", "The", "President", "did", "say", "that", "he", "was", "angry", "about", "this", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "know", "when", "he", "first", "knew", "that", "there", "was", "a", "problem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Well I think it became clear fairly early on the first couple of days that ...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "think", "it", "became", "clear", "fairly", "early", "on", "the", "first", "couple", "of", "days", "that", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "So not before that though?", "question_tokens": ["So", "not", "before", "that", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "There was no concern at that point even the White House or at HHS?", "question_tokens": ["There", "was", "no", "concern", "at", "that", "point", "even", "the", "White", "House", "or", "at", "HHS", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "I think that we talked about having testing going forward and if we had an ideal situation and could've built the product in, you know a five-year period of time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "talked", "about", "having", "testing", "going", "forward", "and", "if", "we", "had", "an", "ideal", "situation", "and", "could", "'ve", "built", "the", "product", "in", ",", "you", "know", "a", "five-year", "period", "of", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "HHS"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "What was your gut feeling when you finish the interview?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "gut", "feeling", "when", "you", "finish", "the", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "I mean, I asked her three separate ways, you know, I mean, and certainly, I'm not the only asking her this question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "asked", "her", "three", "separate", "ways", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "and", "certainly", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "the", "only", "asking", "her", "this", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Did you ever talk about resigning to the President?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "talk", "about", "resigning", "to", "the", "President", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "What I talked about is doing the job that I came here to do.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "talked", "about", "is", "doing", "the", "job", "that", "I", "came", "here", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "If this persist or even at this point now, would you consider resigning over this?", "question_tokens": ["If", "this", "persist", "or", "even", "at", "this", "point", "now", ",", "would", "you", "consider", "resigning", "over", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "I think my job is to get this fully implemented and to get the website working right and that's really what I'm focused on.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "my", "job", "is", "to", "get", "this", "fully", "implemented", "and", "to", "get", "the", "website", "working", "right", "and", "that", "'s", "really", "what", "I", "'m", "focused", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathleen"]}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Well, it's a huge list but I'm a friend of Kathleen's and I'm a friend whenever she's in trouble.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "huge", "list", "but", "I", "'m", "a", "friend", "of", "Kathleen", "'s", "and", "I", "'m", "a", "friend", "whenever", "she", "'s", "in", "trouble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "What is your normal strategy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "normal", "strategy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Occasionally, I have to chop it off, but basically, I believe in sticking by people.", "answer_tokens": ["Occasionally", ",", "I", "have", "to", "chop", "it", "off", ",", "but", "basically", ",", "I", "believe", "in", "sticking", "by", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Howards"]}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "When you look down the line here, what do you feel about these two guys?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "down", "the", "line", "here", ",", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "these", "two", "guys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "I would love to be judged by the two Howards.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "love", "to", "be", "judged", "by", "the", "two", "Howards", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "And I knew then I had a deal because Howard, the Buffett handshake means a lot, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "knew", "then", "I", "had", "a", "deal", "because", "Howard", ",", "the", "Buffett", "handshake", "means", "a", "lot", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Well, what I've learned growing up in our family is that, you know, integrity is everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "I", "'ve", "learned", "growing", "up", "in", "our", "family", "is", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "integrity", "is", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard", "Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Regardless of any bit of paper?", "question_tokens": ["Regardless", "of", "any", "bit", "of", "paper", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Regardless of any piece of paper.", "answer_tokens": ["Regardless", "of", "any", "piece", "of", "paper", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "And do you still prefer to do business with a handshake?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "still", "prefer", "to", "do", "business", "with", "a", "handshake", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Yes, I prefer to do business with people I like.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "prefer", "to", "do", "business", "with", "people", "I", "like", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "But let me ask you, HWB, what is the single best lesson you have learned from the elder Buffetts in your life, so far would you say?", "question_tokens": ["But", "let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "HWB", ",", "what", "is", "the", "single", "best", "lesson", "you", "have", "learned", "from", "the", "elder", "Buffetts", "in", "your", "life", ",", "so", "far", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well both my grandfather and my father have been the most amazing role models that anyone could imagine.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "both", "my", "grandfather", "and", "my", "father", "have", "been", "the", "most", "amazing", "role", "models", "that", "anyone", "could", "imagine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "RP", "CC", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "So we've got plenty of tweets pouring in Jane Fagan Smith (ph) said what's the most important advice you've ever had about investing that you would impart to others?", "question_tokens": ["So", "we", "'ve", "got", "plenty", "of", "tweets", "pouring", "in", "Jane", "Fagan", "Smith", "(", "ph", ")", "said", "what", "'s", "the", "most", "important", "advice", "you", "'ve", "ever", "had", "about", "investing", "that", "you", "would", "impart", "to", "others", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "VBD", "WP", "POS", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, it's to look at stocks as part of the business rather than little things that blob up and down.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "to", "look", "at", "stocks", "as", "part", "of", "the", "business", "rather", "than", "little", "things", "that", "blob", "up", "and", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jane Fagan Smith"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Do you have to personally enjoy the stocks that you buy big in?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "to", "personally", "enjoy", "the", "stocks", "that", "you", "buy", "big", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Well, I enjoyed them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "enjoyed", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "So we used a major rock star writers, there was one request, anything Coca-Cola related?", "question_tokens": ["So", "we", "used", "a", "major", "rock", "star", "writers", ",", "there", "was", "one", "request", ",", "anything", "Coca-Cola", "related", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NN", ",", "NN", "-NONE-", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Coca-Cola"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "How long have you had that one?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "have", "you", "had", "that", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Well, I don't throw anything away until I got it 20 or 25 years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "throw", "anything", "away", "until", "I", "got", "it", "20", "or", "25", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Do you use e-mail?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "use", "e-mail", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "I do it through my assistant.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "it", "through", "my", "assistant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Microsoft"], "LOCATION": ["Minneapolis"], "PERSON": ["Jeff Wright"]}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Who to?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "I sent it to Jeff Wright at Microsoft and it ended up in court in Minneapolis court.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "sent", "it", "to", "Jeff", "Wright", "at", "Microsoft", "and", "it", "ended", "up", "in", "court", "in", "Minneapolis", "court", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Well, it's not so old.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "so", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "You're not into flash things, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "into", "flash", "things", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, I have everything I want, you know, I'm happy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "everything", "I", "want", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "happy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", ":", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "... the rent went down?", "question_tokens": ["...", "the", "rent", "went", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Yeah, and I try to feed him candy and pie and all this ....", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "and", "I", "try", "to", "feed", "him", "candy", "and", "pie", "and", "all", "this", "...", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "So it didn't work?", "question_tokens": ["So", "it", "did", "n't", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "No, not really.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "This deal, I mean it's instinct that the two incentives one worked and one didn't would you regret the weight incentive that you laid down with your son?", "question_tokens": ["This", "deal", ",", "I", "mean", "it", "'s", "instinct", "that", "the", "two", "incentives", "one", "worked", "and", "one", "did", "n't", "would", "you", "regret", "the", "weight", "incentive", "that", "you", "laid", "down", "with", "your", "son", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "CD", "VBD", "CC", "CD", "VBD", "RB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "I would say it was dumb.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "it", "was", "dumb", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Do you have the same criteria?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "the", "same", "criteria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "You know, I don't think I've ever done that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "'ve", "ever", "done", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ"], "qSentId": 239, "question": "You don't seem to face, why?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "seem", "to", "face", ",", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Well, for one thing, if they combine their credits, we can get one degree and that's", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "for", "one", "thing", ",", "if", "they", "combine", "their", "credits", ",", "we", "can", "get", "one", "degree", "and", "that", "'s"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$34 billion"]}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "CD", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "How much did you pay?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "did", "you", "pay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "$34 billion all of it.", "answer_tokens": ["$", "34", "billion", "all", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Do you ever make big mistakes?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "make", "big", "mistakes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Sure, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$400 million"]}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "That's -- If you look back, must be the one you think I should never have done that?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "--", "If", "you", "look", "back", ",", "must", "be", "the", "one", "you", "think", "I", "should", "never", "have", "done", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Well, I bought company in the mid '90s called Dexter's Shoe and paid $400 million for it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "bought", "company", "in", "the", "mid", "'90s", "called", "Dexter", "'s", "Shoe", "and", "paid", "$", "400", "million", "for", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Many say the brains really behind the power, would you agree with that Warren?", "question_tokens": ["Many", "say", "the", "brains", "really", "behind", "the", "power", ",", "would", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "Warren", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "But not you Howard, what did you do?", "question_tokens": ["But", "not", "you", "Howard", ",", "what", "did", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Well, I had a roll of windows in my room and, you know, I open the window up, we had this greenhouse so I'd be careful climbing out because I don't want to go through the glass, but I got down and we had our charge account at the local hardware store about five blocks away and I went up there and I convinced the guy to let me charge a has plaque (ph) and buy a screw driver because I don't have any tools and I get everything I needed and I called back up in and I lock her out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "had", "a", "roll", "of", "windows", "in", "my", "room", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "open", "the", "window", "up", ",", "we", "had", "this", "greenhouse", "so", "I", "'d", "be", "careful", "climbing", "out", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "go", "through", "the", "glass", ",", "but", "I", "got", "down", "and", "we", "had", "our", "charge", "account", "at", "the", "local", "hardware", "store", "about", "five", "blocks", "away", "and", "I", "went", "up", "there", "and", "I", "convinced", "the", "guy", "to", "let", "me", "charge", "a", "has", "plaque", "(", "ph", ")", "and", "buy", "a", "screw", "driver", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "tools", "and", "I", "get", "everything", "I", "needed", "and", "I", "called", "back", "up", "in", "and", "I", "lock", "her", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "How did you mother react?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "mother", "react", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I think as it is, she probably got a kick out of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "as", "it", "is", ",", "she", "probably", "got", "a", "kick", "out", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "How did you change?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "I slowly grew up and I wouldn't otherwise at that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "slowly", "grew", "up", "and", "I", "would", "n't", "otherwise", "at", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Just to override, anything else you would write?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "to", "override", ",", "anything", "else", "you", "would", "write", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Sure, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", ":", "WP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Well, what are the key values that you would like to see other people recognize in your children, your grandchildren, your family or extended family?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "are", "the", "key", "values", "that", "you", "would", "like", "to", "see", "other", "people", "recognize", "in", "your", "children", ",", "your", "grandchildren", ",", "your", "family", "or", "extended", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Well, I want them to be good citizens, good parents that the -- what the world would be better off because they were here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "want", "them", "to", "be", "good", "citizens", ",", "good", "parents", "that", "the", "--", "what", "the", "world", "would", "be", "better", "off", "because", "they", "were", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "What is your definition of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "definition", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Well, I'm not sure I can give you a great one.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "I", "can", "give", "you", "a", "great", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "He said it's thread bare and dust and has cobwebs, right Howard?", "question_tokens": ["He", "said", "it", "'s", "thread", "bare", "and", "dust", "and", "has", "cobwebs", ",", "right", "Howard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "I'm not sure what are the time lock is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "what", "are", "the", "time", "lock", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Howard tell me about this book \"Forty Chances\", why the title?", "question_tokens": ["Howard", "tell", "me", "about", "this", "book", "``", "Forty", "Chances", "''", ",", "why", "the", "title", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Well, the \"Forty Chances\" kind of sort of actually my career farming.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "``", "Forty", "Chances", "''", "kind", "of", "sort", "of", "actually", "my", "career", "farming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "deal", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Well, one of the biggest things I've learned is -- I mean there's a lot of great organizations out there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "of", "the", "biggest", "things", "I", "'ve", "learned", "is", "--", "I", "mean", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "great", "organizations", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Gates Foundation"]}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "What do you make of what he's achieved?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "he", "'s", "achieved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Well, he's operating on a premise as are my other two children and with the Gates Foundation too that all lives have equal value.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "operating", "on", "a", "premise", "as", "are", "my", "other", "two", "children", "and", "with", "the", "Gates", "Foundation", "too", "that", "all", "lives", "have", "equal", "value", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "You're proud of him?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "proud", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I am very proud of him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "very", "proud", "of", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Can you do any better on salary?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "do", "any", "better", "on", "salary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Unfortunately, that ranges at a corporate.", "answer_tokens": ["Unfortunately", ",", "that", "ranges", "at", "a", "corporate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "More on Buffett negotiating with the gang on NBC is the office that led him the attention to details, I'm with his family, one of the most influential in the world back now with the three generations of Buffets, Warren, Howard G, and Howard W. Do you enjoy being actor there, Warren, well you're quite good?", "question_tokens": ["More", "on", "Buffett", "negotiating", "with", "the", "gang", "on", "NBC", "is", "the", "office", "that", "led", "him", "the", "attention", "to", "details", ",", "I", "'m", "with", "his", "family", ",", "one", "of", "the", "most", "influential", "in", "the", "world", "back", "now", "with", "the", "three", "generations", "of", "Buffets", ",", "Warren", ",", "Howard", "G", ",", "and", "Howard", "W.", "Do", "you", "enjoy", "being", "actor", "there", ",", "Warren", ",", "well", "you", "'re", "quite", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNPS", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "ARREN BUFFETT: I wouldn't say that, but nice thing about being mildly famous is that the worst you are the better people like it.", "answer_tokens": ["ARREN", "BUFFETT", ":", "I", "would", "n't", "say", "that", ",", "but", "nice", "thing", "about", "being", "mildly", "famous", "is", "that", "the", "worst", "you", "are", "the", "better", "people", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"], "LOCATION": ["Warren"], "PERSON": ["Howard G", "Howard W.", "Warren"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "If I was to ask you that now what might the answers be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "was", "to", "ask", "you", "that", "now", "what", "might", "the", "answers", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "WP", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Well, I must take a look.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "must", "take", "a", "look", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Is this Edward (inaudible) on television before?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "Edward", "(", "inaudible", ")", "on", "television", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "I got this wallet for -- here's my.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "this", "wallet", "for", "--", "here", "'s", "my", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edward"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "How long have you had it first?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "have", "you", "had", "it", "first", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Probably about 20 years maybe.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "about", "20", "years", "maybe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1964"]}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "And what do you had in it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "do", "you", "had", "in", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Here's my American express card from 1964.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "my", "American", "express", "card", "from", "1964", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "That's the one you have the whole time?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "one", "you", "have", "the", "whole", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Yes, well it goes with my cellphone.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "well", "it", "goes", "with", "my", "cellphone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "What other cards do you have?", "question_tokens": ["What", "other", "cards", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Well, I've variety of card, but there's a picture of the family.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "variety", "of", "card", ",", "but", "there", "'s", "a", "picture", "of", "the", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "JJ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 503, "question": "And how much cash?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "much", "cash", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "More than usual that ...", "answer_tokens": ["More", "than", "usual", "that", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Let me ask you Howard of all the places you've been, of all the issues you've dealt with, what has been the most powerful to you personally?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "Howard", "of", "all", "the", "places", "you", "'ve", "been", ",", "of", "all", "the", "issues", "you", "'ve", "dealt", "with", ",", "what", "has", "been", "the", "most", "powerful", "to", "you", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "The resiliency of people.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "resiliency", "of", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "What is the future for America incorporated, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "future", "for", "America", "incorporated", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Terrific, terrific.", "answer_tokens": ["Terrific", ",", "terrific", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Do you know how much your worth?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "much", "your", "worth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Well, you can multiply the bag of purchase but it's all going to -- it's all going to (inaudible).", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "can", "multiply", "the", "bag", "of", "purchase", "but", "it", "'s", "all", "going", "to", "--", "it", "'s", "all", "going", "to", "(", "inaudible", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Pretty illustrious club, right?", "question_tokens": ["Pretty", "illustrious", "club", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Very few people.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "few", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Frank Sinatra"]}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Have you ever met Frank Sinatra before he died?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "met", "Frank", "Sinatra", "before", "he", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "No, I've never met Frank Sinatra.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'ve", "never", "met", "Frank", "Sinatra", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Frank Sinatra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "You're a fan?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "fan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "And I'm a fan.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "'m", "a", "fan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 578, "question": "And you were fan of ukulele?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "were", "fan", "of", "ukulele", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Yes, and you just have ...", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "you", "just", "have", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "I've been inundating with tweets, many of them are saying these Buffett boys are a lot of fun are they?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "inundating", "with", "tweets", ",", "many", "of", "them", "are", "saying", "these", "Buffett", "boys", "are", "a", "lot", "of", "fun", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "We had a lot fun.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "a", "lot", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "How do you enjoy the last hour?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "enjoy", "the", "last", "hour", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "I've enjoyed it a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "enjoyed", "it", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "to", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "A teacher, teacher.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "teacher", ",", "teacher", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131022pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Which moment would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "moment", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "The time with my dad, that moment, any moment.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "time", "with", "my", "dad", ",", "that", "moment", ",", "any", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]